## Mozes Eisenberg Bl Analyst

055-98-666-31

mozes1001@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mozes-eisenberg

Age: 31

Since 2011 i have been doing BI and business development for food processing organisations. Over the years i have managed to save my employers hundreds of thousands of dollars with intelligently managing and analysing the numbers and other business functions.

I made Aliya in 2018 for personal matters. I am looking to use my experience and knowledge to integrate to a high tech firm needing BI and advanced analysis. I bring a fresh look with an out of the box attitude. I am very serious with my work while being a very good team player adapting myself to the company's direction, culture and needs. I speak 6 languages almost perfect.

I like laughter and fun but only at my lunch break.

### **Work Experience:**

Jan 2018 - Present

Makerthon - The Autonomous Police Station. Participation in a Makerthon(Tech Marathon of the police in collaboration with Oracle) Contributed prototyping study case of IoT into Data Analyze BI bringing up high end technology solution in Smart energy predictable maintenance, with analyzing cost and damages caused not by the customer. The product was successful and appreciated.

#### Jan 2018 - Jan 2019:

Studied at Naya College in Herzliya BI Data Analysis. Completed over 300 Academic hours. Delivered a large Data analysis project for the final exam.

#### May 2013 - Dec 2017:

Business development and Analyst on the ground for **PARDES FARMS LTD** (a US firm). Key responsibilities:

- Learning the existing business process and seek to improve it. Including <u>writing new</u> <u>business standards and procedures for proper workflow.</u>
- Gather Data from over <u>10 manufacturing sites</u>, making sure all data is properly synchronized
- Collaborate and negotiate with Large Firms.
- <u>SETUP And Implement new business process.</u> Including setting up the whole operation on **ZOHO CRM**, **ZOHO Projects**, and **ZOHO FORUM** for feeding data and operational reports through mobile applications.

- Troubleshooting and Crisis Management. I had to solve a very large problem that happened in one of the productions. Because of my carefully built database i managed to save the company almost a million dollars of damage.
- Reports and analyzing creating mobile app collecting data and measures (in 3 Languages ), Generating reports, Process Exploration, lessons learned, implementing in the field.

#### 2011 - 2013

Create and Manage logistic supply chain for a Kosher catering in **Poland** 

Further work history available upon request

# Personal skills and experience:

- Solid Knowledge of Databases, ETL, BI sys, as well various analytical BI tools.
- Business Troubleshooting
- High level experience in characterizing systems and procedures.
- 8 years Business understanding with macro business view
- Solid knowledge of Excel and other Office Tools
- Leading CRM's setup and design experience.
  Specifically: ZOHO Products
- Thinking out of the box
- 6 languages
- Excellent interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently and team player,
- Responsible and loyal.

#### **EDUCATION**

2019: Python Currently Pursuing

2018 - Data Analyst Expert BI, Naya college Graduated with Honors

2016-2017: Self-taught, - Data introduction, UML Modelling

#### COMPUTER SKILLS

- Database: MS SQL Server, MySQL, Advencent SQL TSQL Stored Procedures
- ETL Tools: SSIS SSAS SSRS
- Visaluation & Reports: Tableau, PowerBI, SAS, QlikView, Pivot Advancent

Excel, Zoho: Environments & Tools: Visual Studio, Bash, VM

Languages: English, Dutch, German, Yiddish, Polish Hebrew,

Mandarin